ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- admin/finance planning sheets, program info reports(PIR), Client contracts. (Box 130)
  - Charge Program Agreements + Cornell Univ. - NYSSILR Extension Division Non-Credit Billing Form, 1994-1996 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Charge Program Agreements + Cornell Univ. - NYSSILR Extension Division Non-Credit Billing Form, 1996-1997 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Extension Division Annual Summary of Credit and Non-Credit Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 130, Folder 13)
- Administration inActive File: Adjunct Faculty Personal Data Forms, Independent Contractors. (Box 131)
  - Buczynski, Michael Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Bull, Morris Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1964-1981 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Byrley, Theodore Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Campbell, Thomas Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Campbell, Thomas P Possible Adjunct Instructor, 2001 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Catalano, Claudia Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994-1998 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Chimera, Joseph Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1982 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Clark, Josephine Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Clark, Richard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1996 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Clay, Laverne, 1994-1996 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Clearfield, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-1981 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Cohen-Rosenthal, Edward Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Collins, Bonnie Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1986-1995 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Collins, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1973-1977 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Connelley, Debra Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 1999 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Connelley, Debra Personnel - Adjunct Instructors ( on Payroll), 1999 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Cook, Philip Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Cooperman, Larry Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1996 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Creveling, Constance Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988-1989 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Crivens, Thelma Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Crosby, Kevin Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2001 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Cunningham, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1995 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Dell 'Omo, Gregory Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988-1989 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - Deutschman, Marian Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Doherty, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Drajem, Linda Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - Drescher, Nuala Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1975-1990 (Box 131, Folder 27)
  - Durski, Leonard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 28)
  - Duszkiewicz, Alice Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1983-1984 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Dzierba, Timothy Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 30)
  - Eastwood, Karen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1993-1995 (Box 131, Folder 31)
  - Edwards, Judith Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 32)
  - Fenwick, Bruce Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1985-1987 (Box 131, Folder 33)
  - Finster, Margaret Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979 (Box 131, Folder 34)
  - Fisher, Terry Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 35)
  - Fleckenstein, Marilynn P. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 1998-1999 (Box 131, Folder 36)
  - Fox, Deana Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000-2001 (Box 131, Folder 37)
  - Francisco, Julie R. Personnel - FIRMS/Contractors, 1998 (Box 131, Folder 38)
  - Ganley, William T. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 39)
  - Ganley, William H. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 40)
  - Ganser, Hugh Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1988 (Box 131, Folder 41)
  - Garas, Tena Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 42)
  - Garvin, Deborah Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-1980 (Box 131, Folder 43)
  - Golden, Gail Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994 (Box 131, Folder 44)
  - Goodman, Donald Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1973-1976 (Box 131, Folder 45)
  - Goodwin, William Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 46)
  - Grabowski, Edwin Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1971-1982 (Box 131, Folder 47)
  - Grainger, Richard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 48)
  - Grant, Ellen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1982-1987 (Box 131, Folder 49)
  - Guay, Roland B., 1997 (Box 131, Folder 50)
  - Haley, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 51)
  - Hall, Peter Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 52)
  - Hammond, Bruce Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-1981 (Box 131, Folder 53)
  - Harris, Robert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (Box 131, Folder 54)
  - Hartman Wakshull, Evelyn Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981-1987 (Box 131, Folder 55)
  - Hassberg, Linda Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 56)
  - Hayes, Debora M. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2001 (Box 131, Folder 57)
  - Hertsgaard, Peter Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1993-1998 (Box 131, Folder 58)
  - Hill, David Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1984-1987 (Box 131, Folder 59)
  - Hill, Stephen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 60)
  - Hoepfinger, Karen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1995 (Box 131, Folder 61)
  - Hoover, David Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 1999 (Box 131, Folder 62)
  - Hornung, Mary Jane Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 63)
  - Hudnell, June Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 64)
  - Huffnagle, Melvin P. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1998 (Box 131, Folder 65)
  - Darleen P., Hummert Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1994-1995 (Box 131, Folder 66)
  - Hummert, Richard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1995 (Box 131, Folder 67)
  - Hunter, Jack Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 68)
  - Hurst, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 69)
  - Jackson, Jeffrey Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 70)
  - Jayes, James Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000-2001 (Box 131, Folder 71)
  - Johnson, Carl Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 72)
  - Jinks, Danny Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1982-1983 (Box 131, Folder 73)
  - Jones, Carol Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1990 (Box 131, Folder 74)
  - Jones, Richard Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1982-1987 (Box 131, Folder 75)
  - Justinger, Maryann Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 76)
  - Katz, Harry Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (Box 131, Folder 78)
  - Kester, John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 79)
  - Kleiner, Brian Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 80)
  - Klingel, Sally Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 81)
  - Knoezer, Philip Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1995-1998 (Box 131, Folder 82)
  - Koritz, Douglas Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 83)
  - Korn, Allan Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 84)
  - Kotaska, Joseph Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 85)
  - Kroetsch, Christine Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 86)
  - Kublin, Barry Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 87)
  - Kuchera, Joseph Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 88)
  - LaLonde, Stephen P. Director, Cornell ILR Rochester, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 89)
  - Lanze, Laurie Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 90)
  - Lauerman, David Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 91)
  - Lawson, Beverly Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-1980 (Box 131, Folder 92)
  - Lazes, Peter Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 93)
  - Leary, Thomas Edward, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 94)
  - Levi, Claire Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1979-1980 (Box 131, Folder 95)
  - Lin, William Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 96)
  - Lipsitz, Richard (Senior) Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1989-2001 (Box 131, Folder 97)
  - Rlipsitz, Richard Jr. Resume only, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 98)
  - Lipsky, David Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1991 (Box 131, Folder 99)
  - Logalbo John Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1988 (Box 131, Folder 100)
  - Lomotey, Kofi Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 101)
  - Makai, Susan Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1986-1989 (Box 131, Folder 102)
  - Mangino, Mary Ellen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1991 (Box 131, Folder 103)
  - Martin, Ann Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 104)
  - McDonnell, James Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1973-1977 (Box 131, Folder 105)
  - McDonough, Terrence Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-1989 (Box 131, Folder 106)
  - McKay, Michael W. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1998 (Box 131, Folder 107)
  - Meyerowitz, Ruth Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 108)
  - Millane, Maureen Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (Box 131, Folder 109)
- Proposals Miscellaneous. (Box 132)
  - Different Proposals Related to ILR - Western Region, 2001-2002 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - New Proposals, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Seneca Nation, 2000 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Docs. Related to Automotive Industry Studies, 1999-2001 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - National Grid + ILR, 2002-2006 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - State of NY, Insurance Dept., 2005-2006 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Res. Ext Collab, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Different Grant Proposals + Power Point ILR, 1991-2005 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Monroe Cty, 2004-2006 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Roswell, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - IBEW, 2006 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Ford, 2005-2006 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Different Attachments- ILR Programs, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Charge Program Agreements + Program Proposals, 2003-2004 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Seneca Nation, 2002-2005 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Taking Charge Electric Industry Education Summit Proposal + Supervisory Studies, 1998-2003 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Program Costs?, 1992-2003 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - American Axle, 1995-2000 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - API Fund P/R ED., 2001 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Programs for Ford, 1993-1996 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - AIS 2005 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - AIS 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - SRPP 2004 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - Ford Stampling Plant - Buffalo, NY, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 24)
  - Delph (Harrison) (Box 132, Folder 25)
  - Commerce Dept, 1999-2003 (Box 132, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Color, 1997 (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - Brookings Inst., 2008 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - GM-Harrison Radiator, Dayton, OH, 1989-1990 (Box 132, Folder 29)
  - GM-Harrison Radiator, Lockport, NY, 1988-1995 (Box 132, Folder 30)
  - GM-Harrison Radiator, Sioux City, IA, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 31)
  - GM-Saginaw Steering Gear, Buffalo, NY, 1987-1992 (Box 132, Folder 32)
  - GM-CPC Tonawanda Engine Plant, Buffalo, NY, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 33)
  - PEL - Cornell, 1988-1989 (Box 132, Folder 34)
  - Hoogovens, 1998-1999 (Box 132, Folder 35)
  - Industrial Literacy in the Workplace: Building a Partnership in the Tire Industry, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 36)
  - Joint School Bd. Construction (HUD), 2000 (Box 132, Folder 37)
  - NIMO, 1998 (Box 132, Folder 38)
  - NIMO (Box 132, Folder 39)
  - Labor Relations WNY workers get high marks in Cornell study, 2000 (Box 132, Folder 40)
  - O. American Brass, Redpp, EDPST Grants, 1994-1995 (Box 132, Folder 41)
  - American Brass - Buffalo, NY, 1990-2002 (Box 132, Folder 42)
  - Outokumpu American Brass Program Proposal, 1994-1999 (Box 132, Folder 43)
  - OAB, 1994-1995 (Box 132, Folder 44)
  - Niagara Mohawk, 1993-1999 (Box 132, Folder 45)
  - O CELLO, 1995 (Box 132, Folder 46)
  - Phoenix Construction (Box 132, Folder 47)
  - Roswell, 1998 (Box 132, Folder 48)
  - Sheet Metal, 1999-2001 (Box 132, Folder 49)
  - Telecommunications Forum, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 50)
  - AIS 2005 (Box 132, Folder 51)
  - AIS - 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 132, Folder 52)
  - AIS- UAW-Ford, 1994-2001 (Box 132, Folder 53)
  - UAW - Ford Programs + Documents, 1991-2001 (Box 132, Folder 54)
  - UAW Ford Proposals + Programs, 1992-2002 (Box 132, Folder 55)
  - OAB Connections, 1999 (Box 132, Folder 56)
  - UAW Ford Docs, 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 57)
  - AIS CD Rom Proposal Timeline, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 58)
  - UAW-Ford AIS Programs + Proposals, 1994-1999 (Box 132, Folder 59)
  - Consulting + Conflict of Interest, 1986-1992 (Box 132, Folder 60)
  - Cornell Chronicles + ILR Faculty Docs., 1991-1992 (Box 132, Folder 61)
  - Sales, 2001 (Box 132, Folder 62)
- Credit Prog Registrations. (Box 133)
  - K, 1994-1999 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - L, 1996-1999 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - L, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - MC, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - M, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - M, 1994-1999 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - M, 1994-1999 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - M, 1993-1998 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - N, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - O, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - P, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - P, 1994-1998 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - P, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Q, 1996-1997 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - R, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - R, 1995-1998 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - R, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - S, 1995-1999 (Box 133, Folder 18)
- Program manuals. (Box 134)
  - UAW-GM Local PEL Instr- Part 1 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - UAW -GM Local PEL Instr. Part 2 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - UAW-GM Local PEL (1991) Part 1 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - UAW-GM Local PEL (1991) Part 2 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - UAW-GM-Local PEL (1991) Part 3 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - UAW-GM Local PEL Economic Environment (1997) (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - UAW/Hydromatic Division (1986) (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - UAW-GM Local PEL Strategic Planning (1997) (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - UAW-GM PEL Strategic Planning Vol I (1985) Part 1 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - UAW-GM PEL Strategic Planning Vol I (1985) Part 2 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - UAW-GM Strategic Planning Vol II (1983) Part 1 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - UAW-GM PEL Strategic Planning Vol II (1983) Part 2 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - UAW-GM PEL Strategic Planning Vol III (1986) Part 1, 1984-1986 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - UAW-GM PEL Strategic Planning Vol III (1986) Part 2, 1985-1986 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - UAW-GM PEL Strategic Planning Vol IV (1985) (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Union Leadership Academy (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Unions and International Competition (1991) Part 1 Ver 1 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Unions and International Competition (1991) Part 2 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Unions and International Competition (1991) Part 3 Ver 1 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Unions and International Competition (1991) Part 1 Ver 2 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Unions and International Competition (1991) Part 2 Ver 2 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Unions and International Competition (1991) Part 3 Ver 2 (Box 134, Folder 22)
- Faculty Program MTLS Labor-Labor Law 1&2. (Box 135)
  - National Labor Relations Labor Board Docs., 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Labor Law I - Private Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Session I Lab Law II Fall -86-'87, 1979-1984 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Session 2 - Lab Law II Fall '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Session 3 - Labor Law II, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Session 4 - LL II Fall '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Session 5 - Labor Law II Fall '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Session 6 - Labor Law II Fall '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Session 7 - Labor Law II Fall '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Session 8 - Labor Law II Fall Term '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Session 9 - Labor Law II Fall Term '86-'87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Session II - Labor Law II Fall 1986-87, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Session I, 1984-1987 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Session II, 1974 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Session III, 1985-1986 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Session IV, 1985-1987 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Session V, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Session VI, 1981-1986 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Session VIII, 1985-1987 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - Session IX, 1978-1987 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Session X, 1986-1987 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Employee Rights + Laws, 1981-1990 (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - NY State Dept, of Labor Docs., 1984-1989 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - NY State Right to Know Law Summary Sheet, 1980-1985 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - Doc. Related to Workers' Comp, 1985-1990 (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - Law of Employment Practices + Other Docs., 1986-1991 (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Housing Rulings on Inquiries + Sexual Harassment Pamphlet, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - Law of Employment Practices Fall 1992 Materials Orders (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - Docs. Related to Discrimination+ Human Rights, 1986-1988 (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - Public Sector Law + PERB, 1987-1988 (Box 135, Folder 30)
  - CHIP 8th FL Personnel, 1988-1990 (Box 135, Folder 31)
- Library program manuals - Education technologist files-from faculty programs. (Box 136)
  - SS (KMH) 95W116 Effective Business Writing (210-082-01) Jan. 17 - Mar. 20, 1996 Grippi (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - SS (MYV) 95W114 Business + Professional Speaking (210-246-01) Sept.. 20 - Dec. 13, 1995 Regan (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - SS (BMH) 95W115 Oral Communications (210-083-01) Oct. 19 - Dec. 12, 1995 Purtan Roy, 1991-1995 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Studies (MYV) 95W101 Human Resource Planning + Strategy Sept. 15 - Dec. 2, 1995 Morano (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - SS (MYV) 95W110-111 Written Communications (210-082) Sept. 19 - Dec. 12, 1995 Regan (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - BLS 97W160 Effective Interviewing: Legal and Human Resource Skills For Practioners Scott Aviation June 8-9, 1998 Lundquist (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - BLS - Cornell ILR Labor History - Blair, 1996 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - LS (IUOE Local 17) 96W100-101 Labor History (200-011-01-02) July 19 - Aug. 8, 1996 Blair (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - BLS 96W124 Comparative Labor Movement (200-057-01) Jan. 9, 1997 Blair (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - BLS (MYV) 96W112 Labor History (200-011-01) Sept. 19 - Dec. 12, 1996 Blair (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - BLS (MYV) 95W103 Labor History (200-011-01) Sept. 21 - Dec. 14, 1995 Blair (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - BLS (MYV) 96W114 Labor, Govern. + Politics (200-087-01) Sept. 19 - Dec. 12, 1996 Fleron, 1990-1996 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - BLS (MYV) 96W114 Labor, Govern. + Politics (200-087-01) Sept. 19 - Dec. 12, 1996 Fleron, 1995-1996 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - SS (MYV) 96W106-107 Written Communications (210-082) Sept. 17 - Dec. 10, 1996 Regan SS ( (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - SS (MYV) 95W137 Oral Communications (210-083-01) Apr.2 - May 28, 1996 Regan ay 28 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - SS (MYV) 95W138 Oral Communications (210-083-02) Apr. 4 - May 30, 1996 Grippi (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Student Correspondence F'95-SS Western Region Certificate Programs Student Handbook 1995-96, 1995-1996 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Language Development Program 97W056 Interpersonal Skills 10/10/97 + 10/29/97 Henderson, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Crime, Violence + The Judicial System Fleron Fall 1996 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - SS (VA) 96W118 Intro. To Financial Mgmt. (210-064-01) Oct.9 - Dec. 11, 1996 DeNisco (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - BLS (MYV) 95W127 Labor Law I: Private Sector (200-014-01) Jan. 11-Mar. 28, 1996 Grande, 1995-1996 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - BLS (MYV) 95W105 Labor Law II (200-089-01) Sept. 21 - Dec. 14, 1995 Reden (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - BLS (MYV) 96W113 Labor Law II (200-089-01)) Sept. 19 - Dec. 12, 1996 Grande, 1994-1996 (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - GS 96W116 Employment Law (202-655-01) Oct. 2 - Dec. 18, 1996 Schmit (Box 136, Folder 24)
  - BLS 96W127 Labor Law I: Public Sector (200-042-01) Jan. 9, 1997 Poch (Box 136, Folder 25)
  - BLS 96W126 Labor Law I: Private Sector (200-01407) Jan. 1, 1997 Reden (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - BLS 96W129 Survey in Worker Participation (210-069-01) Feb. 1, 1997 Woods, 1994-1997 (Box 136, Folder 27)
  - BLS (MYV) 95W129 Survey in Worker Participation (200-069-01) Jan. 20 - Feb. 17, 1996 Woods, 1994-1997 (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Industry Studies WNY Employee Invovement Council December 2, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 29)
  - GS 96W130 Leadership in Organizations (202-627-01)- Jan. 15 0 Apr. 16, 1997 Elgie-Levan, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 30)
  - GS (MYV) 96W117 Org. Change + Intervention (202-729-01) Sept. 20 - Nov. 23, 1996 Morano (Box 136, Folder 31)
  - SS (MYV) 95W122 Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior (210-092-03) Jan. 9 - Mar. 26, 1996 Ahearn (Box 136, Folder 32)
  - GRD (MYV) 95W125 Employee Relations (202-667-01) Jan. 19 - Mar. 30, 1996 Stanger, 1993-1996 (Box 136, Folder 33)
  - BLS (MYV) 95W104 Legal + Org. Basis for Corp. Power Sept.21 - Dec. 14, 1995 Sholes (Box 136, Folder 34)
- Faculty-Grogan, Regina Central NY LM Grant. (Box 137)
  - Docs. Relating to NY State Dept. of Labor, Taylor Law, Unions, etc., 1999-2009 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Docs. Relating to NY State Dept. of Labor, CLASP, AFL-CIO, 2003-2008 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Docs. Relating to Work + the Economy in New York State, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Docs. Relating to Steelworkers, Autoworkers, Immigrant Workforce- Grogan, 2004-2007 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Summary for mtg + Comment Industries 9/08 Diversity Distributions, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Central NY Photos + Releases, 2008-2009 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Detailed Statistics = American Factfinder, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - NAICS- CNY Project, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - 2008 Union Rates, 2008-2009 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Part-Time Statistics - Background CNY Paycheck, 2001-2008 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Oswego County, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Cayuga County, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Cortland County, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Madison County, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Onondaga County, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Other Background Info, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - CNY- Union Data Base, 2006-2008 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Onondaga County Proposal, 2004-2007 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - CNY Letters to Survey Participants, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - CNY Questionnaires - Final, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - CNY Project IRB Paperwork +OSP, 2007-2009 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - CNY Pilot Study Documents, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - CNY Codebook- Union, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - CNY Codebook- Employers, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - CNYL-M Project SRI Communication, 2004-2009 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - Graphs + Layout (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - Sassy Design CNY Project, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - Public Private Sector - Data Splits, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 28)
- admin/finance planning sheets, program info reports(PIR), Client contracts; Program Files-Credit, SS. (Box 138)
  - PIR YE June 97 - June 98, 1997-1998 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Planning Sheets 7/1/99-6/30/00 "organized by calendar date as a way of prioritizing processing of counters, in voices, instant payment + tracking it all by fileform program #" (1), 1999-2000 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Planning Sheets 7/1/99-6/30/00 (2), 1999-2000 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Planning Sheets 7/1/99-6/30/00 (3), 1999-2000 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - UAW-GM HRC 95W098 The Auto Industry in Transition (PEL) 4/22 - 4/25/96 Blair, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - The Carborundum Company 95W093 Carborundum Supervisory Studies 2/26/96 - 5/13/96 Henderson, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Auto Alliance International 95W094-97 L/M Studies: Value + Strengths 2/8/96 - 3/7/96 Murak, 1996 (Box 138, Folder 7)